pixelsurplus.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy — Pixel Surplus | Resources For Designers

At Pixel Surplus (www.pixelsurplus.com), one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains details regarding the type of information that is collected and recorded by Pixel Surplus and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us through email at [hello@pixelsurplus.com](mailto:hello@pixelsurplus.com)

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Pixel Surplus. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

### Log Files

Pixel Surplus follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Like any other website, Pixel Surplus uses 'cookies'. These cookies are used to store information including visitors' preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users' experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors' browser type and/or other information.

### Third-party ad servers

Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Pixel Surplus, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that Pixel Surplus has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

 **Google DoubleClick DART Cookie -** Google is a third-party vendor on our site. It uses cookies, known as DART cookies, to serve ads to our site visitors based upon their visits to other sites on the internet. However, visitors may choose to decline the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following URL – <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>

### Third Party Privacy Policies

The Pixel Surplus Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. 

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To find out more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, please refer to your browsers' respective websites. 

### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
